consumermate.com 2013-06-15

# Privacy Policy

Home \- Privacy Policy 

###  Our commitment to privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect this privacy we provide notices explaining our online information practices. The information collected

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our website. We collect only such information from you as necessary to provide products and services to you from our website. On some pages you can make request to receive information on products or services or register to become a regular member of the website. Information collected on these pages include:

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Phone no
  * Address

In general, the system allows us to automatically gather information that does not identify you personally, like the date and time of your visit and the pages you visit. It also allows us gather information on the type of browser you are using (like Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of Operating System you are using (like Windows '98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet Service

Provider (like VSNL, Airtel, Satyam Online). We sometimes use this non-personally identifiable information to improve our website design, content and primarily to give you a better browsing experience.

The information you provide is not given or sold to any private organisations or private persons without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law.

####  Personal Information

In the course of requesting best quotes of prices on the technology gadgets and availing various services through Consumermate.com you may be required to give your name, email address, mobile number and similar "Personal Information". When you express an interest in purchasing a laptop, mobile phone, lcd/plasma tv, digital camera and/or camcorder or request for best quotes from the dealers or stores, the dealers or the stores will be forwarded your contact information. They in turn will contact you through email or SMS to fulfil your requests and offer you best quotes. At the same time vendor details will also be communicated to you by Consumermate via email or SMS or both.

When you submit any enquiry on the website for receiving best quotes or otherwise, it is deemed that you are agreeing to receive communication from Consumermate or dealers and stores affiliated with Consumermate electronically, in the form of mail or SMS or any other way.

####  Indemnity

You irrevocably and unconditionally grant to Consumermate.com (and those authorised by it) all necessary rights and consents for the full period of copyright to use any Content you submit for any purposes, and this shall include without limitation the ability for

Consumermate.com to copy, adapt, digitize, encode, publish and transmit the Content across its network and on websites owned or controlled by it and otherwise to use and exploit the Content in any way in any media and in any part of the world. Such right to use is royalty-free and no payment is, or shall be, due to you. You grant to Consumermate.com the non-exclusive right to syndicate your Content to third party websites or services. You permit Consumermate.com and its third party agents to edit or change the Content in any way that they deem necessary in their sole discretion.

####  Use of the information

We use the information you provide about yourself when you are requesting for more information, or are buying a product or service from our partners, affiliates or third party site, only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

Information submitted to us is only available to our employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you e-mails or any other service, for information or services sought by you. We use non-identifying information to design our website and share the same with advertisers. We do not disclose any thing that could be used to identify those individuals. We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone.

####  Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

Our website sometimes contains links to other websites whose privacy policies may be different to ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. We also use a reputable third party to serve the advertisements that you see on our pages. In the course of serving advertisements, our third-party advertiser may place or recognise a unique "cookie" on your browser and may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

####  Links to Other Sites

Our website has links to other website(s) in the World Wide Web. The privacy policies of these website(s) is not under our control. Once you leave our servers, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. It is advisable to read their privacy policies for further information.

####  Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

9.9 Mediaworx Private Limited and Consumermate.com reserves the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted on the web site. The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on August 21, 2009.
